

Phattanothai Pukham

Software Developer

Personal Information

Nick Name Fluke **Military Status** Reservist **Immediately Date of Availaility**

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

Tel	0635957755
Email	phattanothai.pukham@gmail.com
Address	96 Moo.6 Tambon
	Thanthong, Amphur Phan,
	Chiang Rai 57250
Github	https://github.com/phattanotai
Website	https://phattanothai-pukham-
	web.netlify.app

Skilla

Graphic	Design	
Fair		
UX/UI D	esign	
Fair		
Coding		
	Fluent	
Databa s	se se	
Good		
Server		
Standard		
Researc	h	
	Excellent	

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

WORK EXPERIENCE

1 Aug. 2022 - Present Frontend Developer at Driven Digital Co., Ltd.

(Web App)

Jan. 2022 - Present Freelance Software Developer (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API)

1 Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2022 Full Stack Developer Full-Time (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API) at OTEN

INNOVATION, (Remote Work) 1 Jun. 2019 - 31 Oct. 2020

tcp server, REST API) at World Gps Tracker

Programmer Full-Time (Web App, Mobile App,

Co.,Ltd, Chiang Rai http://wgtgps.net

1 May 2017 - 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

ABILITIES

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, Ionic, Nuxtjs, React Native, Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet, sms, email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

> Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Kubernetes, Docker, Kong Server

Api Gateway, GCP, AWS

Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack, Tools

CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana,

gRPC, RabbitMQ

Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache Research

Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, SwiftUI, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM